The target is located on the Airport Highway.
목표는 공항 고속도로에 있습니다.
Du Tao
두 타오
let's go now
이제 가자
Tian Yang
양 티안
We look for Dudo's luggage.
우리는 Dudo의 수하물을 찾습니다.
Secret file not found
비밀 파일을 찾을 수 없습니다
The thing is
문제는
I suspect it broke in the bathroom.
화장실에서 고장난 것 같아요.
How is that person doing?
그 사람은 어떻게 지내요?
sudden coma
갑작스런 혼수상태
i was taken to hospital
나는 병원으로 이송됐어
Puzzled?
어찌할 바를 모르는?
Yes
예
You also have to watch out for comas.
혼수상태도 조심해야 합니다.
Waiting for my letter
내 편지를 기다리고 있어요
Yes
예
Dudo has been exposed
Dudo가 노출되었습니다.
take care of everything
모든 것을 잘 처리해
ok let's go
확인 가자
Who is this?
누구세요?
boss
사장
I don't want to get caught by the government
정부한테 잡히기 싫어
I did not say
나는 말하지 않았다
I didn't say anything
난 아무 말도 안 했어
The dead are safest
죽은 사람이 가장 안전하다
I've taken care of things.
나는 일을 처리했습니다.
if they catch me
만약 그들이 나를 잡으면
There's nothing they can do, really.
정말 그들이 할 수 있는 일은 아무것도 없습니다.
How did you deal with it?
어떻게 처리하셨나요?
bags
바지
I am
그래요
J63 I put it in my travel bag.
J63 여행가방에 넣었어요.
I am now
나는 지금
I can't confirm what you said
당신이 말한 내용을 확인할 수 없습니다
if you find the passenger
승객을 찾으면
i can bring something
내가 뭔가를 가져올 수 있어요
I swearI swear
맹세해요맹세해요
What I said is real
내가 한 말이 진짜야
this is not a lie
이건 거짓말이 아니야
please let me go
가게 해 줘
please
제발
Do you know who sent me?
나에게 보낸 사람이 누구인지 아시나요?
That's right, I'll let you go
그렇구나, 널 보내줄게
Boss Zhang
장보스
Did Boss Zhang send this to you?
장보스가 이걸 보냈나요?
Don't shoot, please don't shoot
쏘지 마세요, 쏘지 마세요
don't shoot
쏘지 마세요
We had a good chat.
우리는 좋은 대화를 나눴습니다.
We'll talk more later.
나중에 더 이야기하겠습니다.
Did you speak again?
또 말했어?
Hello Mr. Yu
안녕하세요 유씨님
What happened there?
거기서 무슨 일이 일어 났어?
Yes
예
Thank you for your cooperation
도와 주셔서 감사합니다
ophthalmology
안과학
thank you and well done
감사하고 잘했어요
research content
연구 내용
The contents of the memory card are sealed.
메모리 카드의 내용은 밀봉되어 있습니다.
Unlock secrets quickly
빠르게 비밀을 풀어보세요
Already ruined
이미 망가졌어
No need to insist
고집할 필요는 없어
I have found the card
카드를 찾았어요
As long as you cooperate
당신이 협력하는 한
If you find someone better
더 좋은 사람 만나면
even if you hit the ball
공을 쳐도
you know very well
당신은 아주 잘 알고
Get off work early
일찍 퇴근하세요
I don't want to waste time either
나도 시간낭비하고 싶지 않아
I just take care of my stuff
난 내 물건만 챙겨요
I don't know what else
다른 건 모르겠는데
You know who wants to kill you
당신은 누가 당신을 죽이고 싶어하는지 알고 있습니다
Are you pretending not to know?
모르는 척 하는 거야?
Who is your boss?
당신의 상사는 누구입니까?
The manager is my superior.
매니저는 내 상사야.
usually
대개
This is my mission
이것이 나의 사명이다
This item
이 아이템
Where did you get it?
어디서 구했어요?
Who are the visitors?
방문자는 누구입니까?
These items were brought from Zhenhai Library.
이 자료는 진해도서관에서 가져온 것입니다.
The interviewer really doesn't know.
면접관은 정말 모릅니다.
I've never really seen it
나는 그것을 실제로 본 적이 없다.
But I have his phone number.
하지만 나는 그 사람 전화번호를 알고 있어요.
professor
교수
How did you meet Chairman Zhang?
장 회장을 어떻게 만났나요?
Have you contacted the professor?
교수님한테 연락은 해보셨나요?
I'm with them
나는 그들과 함께 있어요
We all connect through games.
우리는 모두 게임을 통해 연결됩니다.
what game?
무슨 게임?
special attack mission
특수 공격 임무
This is the game
이것은 게임이다
but I
하지만 나는
I registered his game account.
나는 그의 게임 계정을 등록했습니다.
It has been canceled
취소되었습니다
The other party responded quickly
상대방이 빠르게 반응함
this is what it looks like
이게 그 모습이야
I'm playing a game
나는 게임을하고있다
I don't believe anything
나는 아무것도 믿지 않는다
That's right, he's here again
그렇구나, 그 사람 또 왔어
continue
계속하다
What's in the game
게임에는 무엇이 들어있나요?
special forces training
특수부대 훈련
train?
기차?
what game is this?
이게 무슨 게임이에요?
The question is
질문은 ~이야
I just found someone who can answer
방금 대답해줄 수 있는 사람을 찾았어요
Director Jin
진 이사
let me introduce you to
에게 당신을 소개 할게요
This person is from the Holy Office
이 사람은 성직에서 왔습니다
Wuxi tide
우시 조수
Special attack game case
특수 공격 게임 케이스
It's already raining
벌써 비가 내리고 있어요
I've been following you for a while
나는 한동안 당신을 따라다녔어요
Next
다음
Let Wuxi introduce it to you.
우시(Wuxi)에서 소개해드립니다.
is that so
그렇습니까?
OK
좋아요
Sit morning and evening
아침저녁으로 앉아서
Do you need a computer?
컴퓨터가 필요합니까?
The special mission is
특별 임무는
Developed abroad
해외에서 개발
Online game
온라인 게임
on dark sites
어두운 사이트에서
It's been running for a while.
그것은 한동안 실행되었습니다.
Virtual Special Forces World
가상 특수부대 세계
We created a virtual world of Special Forces.
우리는 특수부대의 가상 세계를 만들었습니다.
Attracted many players
많은 플레이어의 관심을 끌었습니다.
But this game
하지만 이 게임은
The man behind the scenes is
무대 뒤의 남자는
Awesome spy organization Yamu
멋진 스파이 조직 야무
In the name of the game they
게임의 이름으로 그들은
Tempt and engage players
플레이어를 유혹하고 참여시키세요
espionage
스파이 활동
At the same time, it is also night fog
동시에 밤안개이기도 하다.
This is how we choose new spies.
이것이 우리가 새로운 스파이를 선택하는 방법입니다.
are you ready?
준비 되었나요?
Yes
예
Game is special attack
게임은 특수공격이다
rather than a game
게임보다는
more
더
It's like a virtual special forces world
가상의 특수부대 세계 같아요
attract targets
표적을 유인하다
About the career of special forces
특수부대 경력에 대해서
interested young people
관심 있는 젊은이들
Although this is an important game
중요한 경기임에도 불구하고
Currently, global users
현재 글로벌 사용자
Still increasing
계속 증가 중
The current player is
현재 플레이어는
Breaking through 1 million
100만 돌파
when you enter the game
게임에 들어갈 때
There will be a first task
첫 번째 과제가 있을 거예요
novice player
초보 플레이어
you have to go through this door
이 문으로 들어가야 해
You can enter the game main map
게임 메인맵에 입장할 수 있습니다
I'm really crazy
나 정말 미쳤어
I'm here to go on a routine mission with you.
나는 당신과 함께 일상적인 임무를 수행하기 위해 여기에 있습니다.
If someone is missing two coins
누군가 동전 두 개를 잃어버렸다면
Can I get premium assignments?
프리미엄 과제를 받을 수 있나요?
admit defeat
패배를 인정하다
Bring it quickly
빨리 가져와
Where?
어디?
Let's go on a high level mission.
높은 레벨의 미션을 진행해보자.
Let me think.
생각해보자.
When it comes to making money, what are you worried about?
돈을 벌 때 어떤 고민을 하시나요?
I will go
나는 갈 것이다
money tree
돈나무
Beginner level of the game
게임의 초급 수준
All types of gamers
모든 유형의 게이머
You can choose online tasks suitable for your level
자신의 수준에 맞는 온라인 작업을 선택할 수 있습니다.
The purpose of the online tasks is to
온라인 작업의 목적은 다음과 같습니다.
bring games
게임을 가져오다
Educating Casual Gamers
캐주얼 게이머 교육
This is the basic skill of a spy.
이것이 스파이의 기본 스킬이다.
PlayerDinahwang
Player디나황
Pass level 27
레벨 27 통과
Gamer Kang Xiaohua
게이머 강샤오화
Pass level 28
레벨 28 통과
For example
예를 들어
Simple cremation survey
간단한 화장 조사
sufficient responsiveness
충분한 대응력
Teamwork skills
팀워크 기술
Tool-specific operations
도구별 작업
Advanced tasks
고급 작업
Apply for 100 yuan
100위안 신청
Prize: 800 yuan
상금 : 800위안
Mission Objective Mr. Yamamoto
임무 목표 야마모토 씨
Mission details
임무 세부정보
within 10 minutes
10분 이내
Military information on him
그에 대한 군사 정보
The secret hidden in the waist
허리에 숨겨진 비밀
The Scar of the Message Bearer
메시지 전달자의 상처
quit
그만두다
Congratulations on completing your mission.
임무 완수를 축하드립니다.
Reward has been deposited
보상이 입금되었습니다
game tasks
게임 작업
You can also win generous prizes
푸짐한 경품도 받아보실 수 있어요
Your level is getting higher and higher
레벨이 점점 높아지네요
We will also double the bonus.
보너스도 두 배로 지급하겠습니다.
the most important is
가장 중요한 것은
The game currency is
게임 화폐는
You can exchange it for real money
실제 돈으로 교환할 수 있어요
The current price is
현재 가격은
Exchange U.S. dollars one-to-one
미국 달러를 1대1로 교환하세요
this is the game
이게 게임이야
This is what fascinates me the most
이것이 나를 가장 매료시킨다.
how about this?
이건 어때?
50,000 won
50,000원
I can't believe I wrote this
내가 이런 글을 썼다니 믿을 수 없다
Is it too creepy?
너무 소름 끼치나요?
This is the fifth anniversary limited edition
5주년 기념 한정판이에요
Save it every day
매일 저장해두세요
risking one's life on mission
목숨을 걸고 임무를 수행하다
currently
현재
tell me if it's cool
괜찮은지 말해줘
one letter
한 글자
purchase
구입
very cool
아주 멋지다
Dad, let's go get some air.
아빠, 바람 좀 쐬러 가세요.
If you hear something like this
이런 얘기 들으면
I think it's a game
내 생각엔 이건 게임인 것 같아
This is just a beginner level
이건 그냥 초보 수준이에요
Players are at a beginner level
플레이어가 초급 수준입니다.
immediately
즉시
Complete online game missions
온라인 게임 임무를 완료하세요
But there are also many online game players
하지만 온라인 게임 플레이어도 많습니다.
every gamer
모든 게이머
You can't be a real spy
넌 진짜 스파이가 될 수 없어
But all gamers
하지만 모든 게이머는
Every
모든
This will be the goal of the Night Mist organization.
이것이 Night Mist 조직의 목표가 될 것입니다.
Excuse me, please.
실례합니다.
So what about these players?
그렇다면 이 선수들은 어떨까요?
Can you be a spy?
당신은 스파이가 될 수 있나요?
Offline tasks
오프라인 작업
I received an invitation
초대장을 받았습니다
This is a request from Ace Club.
에이스클럽의 요청사항입니다.
You are the ace special attack
당신은 에이스 특수 공격입니다
You have been qualified to participate in offline mission challenges
오프라인 미션챌린지에 참가할 수 있는 자격을 갖추셨습니다.
Offline tasks
오프라인 작업
Ace Special Offline Mission Challenge
에이스 스페셜 오프라인 미션 챌린지
successful gamer
성공한 게이머
You will receive a thousand dollar bonus.
천 달러의 보너스를 받게 됩니다.
But the game content is
하지만 게임 내용은
always keep things mysterious
항상 모든 것을 신비하게 유지하세요
Ace special attack
에이스 특수 공격
person who gets this position
이 직책을 맡은 사람
You will become a legend in the game
당신은 게임의 전설이 될 것입니다
Many gamers were also attracted.
많은 게이머들도 매료되었습니다.
that's right
좋아요
secret
비밀
Offline games are full of yearning
오프라인 게임에는 그리움이 가득하다
100,000 bonus
100,000 보너스
But the players don’t know
하지만 선수들은 모른다.
them
그들을
When you start an offline game
오프라인 게임을 시작할 때
they already
그들은 이미
They said it was captured by the Nightmist group.
Nightmist 그룹이 캡쳐했다고 하더군요.
Which
어느
A person who has obtained the special attack ace level
특수공격 에이스 등급을 획득한 자
About nightlife organizations
유흥단체에 대하여
He is a very valuable person.
그는 매우 귀중한 사람입니다.
The Anglican Church has
성공회 교회는
this game
이 게임
i have a mission
나에겐 임무가 있어
Deeper into the game
게임에 더 깊이 빠져들다
Investigate the players involved
관련 플레이어 조사
In Zhenhai
진하이에 위치
drag away
끌어내다
Ace special attack
에이스 특수 공격
code
암호
professor
교수
In the hands of Du Tao
두타오의 손에
that information
그 정보
All provided by professors.
모두 교수가 제공한 것입니다.
Yes
예
So what kind of character is Du Tao?
그렇다면 두타오는 어떤 캐릭터일까요?
Du Tao is just an ordinary game player.
Du Tao는 평범한 게임 플레이어입니다.
Game numbers have depth
게임 번호에는 깊이가 있습니다
After development
개발 후
Transport information
교통정보
Professor Li in the competition
대회에 참가한 리 교수
Faceless
얼굴 없는
No contact with other players
다른 플레이어와 접촉하지 않음
find professor
교수를 찾아
in game
게임 중
I started contacting Dudo.
나는 Dudo에게 연락하기 시작했습니다.
his
그의
Find basic information
기본정보 찾기
Step by step
단계별로
in real life
현실에서
identity
신원
Du Duo's actions are
듀오의 행보는
arrested professor
체포 교수
This is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
이건 일생에 한 번뿐인 기회야
so we follow him
그래서 우리는 그를 따라간다
I came to Zhenhai Library
진해도서관에 왔어요
the woman on the screen
화면 속의 여자
Just in two ditches
딱 두 도랑에
A person who obtains information from a library
도서관에서 정보를 얻는 사람
Is this person a professor?
이 사람이 교수인가요?
Yes
예
But unfortunately
하지만 불행하게도
CCTV footage cannot be captured
CCTV 영상은 캡쳐가 안되네요
I can't find any features about her
나는 그녀에 대한 어떤 특징도 찾을 수 없습니다
with her
그녀와 함께
Library Roadmap
도서관 로드맵
I stepped on it early.
일찍 밟았네요.
So I didn't find it
그래서 못찾았어
i can't find it
나는 그것을 찾을 수 없다
I have another question
다른 질문이 있어요
explain
설명하다
Du Tao said he gave me a mission.
두 타오가 나에게 임무를 주었다고 하더군요.
That person's name is President Zhang.
그 사람 이름은 장 회장이에요.
So who is this business owner?
그렇다면 이 사업주는 누구일까요?
And Boss Zhang
그리고 장보스
This is a character in the game.
게임에 등장하는 캐릭터입니다.
we are
우리는
Behind the Gamers
게이머 뒤에
There is a trace of President Jang there.
그곳에는 장 회장의 흔적이 있다.
so
그래서
President Zhang in the night fog.
밤안개 속의 장회장.
Addicted to the game
게임에 중독됨
VIP
요인
he played the game
그는 게임을 했어요
Monitor players
플레이어 모니터링
We are announcing orders from behind the scenes.
우리는 뒤에서 명령을 발표하고 있습니다.
So this professor
그럼 이 교수는
Has he improved?
그 사람이 좋아졌나요?
Yes
예
so we
그래서 우리는
In Zhenhai
진하이에 위치
Hide strict spy sites
엄격한 스파이 사이트 숨기기
President Li Zhang
리 장 회장
I'm responsible for the Internet.
저는 인터넷을 담당하고 있습니다.
all
모두
Are you a person in the game?
당신은 게임 속 사람인가요?
So in real life
그래서 실생활에서
Probably in Zhenhai.
아마도 진하이(Zhenhai)에 있을 겁니다.
that's right
좋아요
so now
그래서 지금
we are
우리는
I had no choice but to start with the hidden spy player
숨겨진 스파이 플레이어부터 시작할 수밖에 없었어요
I have received instructions from my superiors.
나는 상사로부터 지시를 받았습니다.
A dedicated team has been established
전담팀이 구성됐다.
I will be the team leader.
나는 팀의 리더가 될 것이다.
About special attack game
특수 공격 게임에 대해
We are conducting a comprehensive investigation
종합적인 조사를 진행하고 있습니다
Professor Du Tao
두 타오 교수
This might just be the tip of the iceberg
이건 빙산의 일각일지도
but we
하지만 우리는
Toward a breakthrough
돌파구를 향해
Let's dig into the entire internet of spies
스파이 인터넷 전체를 파헤쳐보자
Gao Tianyang got permission from his superiors.
Gao Tianyang은 상사로부터 허가를 받았습니다.
This dedicated team
이 전담팀
Deputy head
부국장
Wuxi cooperates with your work
Wuxi는 귀하의 업무에 협력합니다.
Have you collaborated before?
이전에 협력한 적이 있나요?
we cooperated
우리는 협력했다
wave
파도
computer expert
컴퓨터 전문가
I am also a game master
나도 게임마스터다
for all of us
우리 모두를 위해
provide technical support
기술 지원을 제공하다
One day you can cooperate
언젠가 협력할 수 있을 거야
Yes
예
let us do our best
우리 최선을 다하자
Hello, my account is Seokdu.
안녕하세요 제 계정은 석두입니다.
Then everyone called me Seokdu.
그러다 다들 나를 석두라고 불렀다.
Director Jin Eye Clinic
진안과 원장
Memory card contents
메모리 카드 내용
I solved the secret
비밀을 풀었어요
this
이것
I think this is experimental data.
실험적인 데이터인 것 같아요.
stop
멈추다
Analyze information as quickly as possible
최대한 빠르게 정보를 분석하세요.
Find sources of experimental data
실험 데이터의 출처 찾기
How long does it take?
얼마나 시간이 걸려요?
please send me the data
나에게 데이터를 보내주세요
I'll be done in about an hour.
한 시간쯤 후에 끝나겠습니다.
After hearing the news from Chairman Zhang,
장 회장의 소식을 듣고
In Zhenhai
진하이에 위치
The player responsible for transportation
운송을 담당하는 플레이어
i lost contact
연락이 끊겼어
Fortunately
다행스럽게도
Because I haven’t contacted anyone offline
오프라인으로 아무한테도 연락한 적 없으니까
Already opened a game account
이미 게임 계정을 개설했습니다
I canceled
취소했습니다
If you lose a regular player
일반 플레이어를 잃으면
not give a damn about
신경쓰지마
Protecting our samples is of utmost importance.
샘플을 보호하는 것이 가장 중요합니다.
Please tell Chairman Zhang.
장 회장에게 말씀해 주십시오.
don't wait any longer
더 이상 기다리지 마세요
Steal samples now
지금 샘플을 훔치세요
Boss Zhang
장보스
I told the professor to get the sample.
교수님한테 샘플을 받아오라고 했어요.
The result will be out soon
결과는 곧 나올 거예요
that's right
좋아요
Zhenhai District Map
전하이구 지도
You say there aren't enough transport vehicles.
운송수단이 부족하다고 하더군요.
I can move this guy.
이 사람을 움직일 수 있어요.
He is from Zhenhai District
그는 전하이(鎭海)구 출신이다.
This is a key development goal.
이것이 주요 개발 목표입니다.
Next Ace Special Attack
다음 에이스 특수 공격
Effective immediately
즉시 적용
Yes
예
Please pass verification.
인증을 통과해주세요.
verification failed
확인 실패
let's do it together
같이 하자
you are not invited
당신은 초대받지 않았습니다
go back
돌아가다
i will find the way
내가 길을 찾아볼게
I
나
I will go
나는 갈 것이다
open the door
문을 열어라
I really want to go
정말 가고 싶어요
Come in
올
welcome
환영
Lucky Dina
럭키 디나
you are the boss
당신은 상사입니다
from now on
지금부터
I am
그래요
Offline in offline tasks
오프라인 작업에서 오프라인
Boss Zhang
장보스
So are you a real person?
그럼 당신은 진짜 사람인가요?
Or is it a game character?
아니면 게임 캐릭터인가요?
As you get deeper into the game
게임에 깊이 빠져들수록
my identity
내 정체성
I will reveal it slowly
천천히 공개할게요
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
your mission
당신의 임무
whenever
언제든지
I will send it to the application
신청서에 보내드립니다
Be careful with your collection
컬렉션에 주의하세요
and
그리고
When performing offline tasks
오프라인 작업을 수행할 때
you will have a partner
당신은 파트너를 갖게 될 것입니다
i have a partner
나에겐 파트너가 있어요
men and women?
남자와 여자?
Isn't this Jiang Suhua?
장쑤화 아닌가요?
You will find out then
그러면 알게 될 거야
I am
그래요
I like James Band
나는 제임스 밴드를 좋아한다.
I don't really like Pollock House.
나는 폴락 하우스를 별로 좋아하지 않는다.
What you need is Bang Yeorang
너에게 필요한 건 방여랑
Not reincarnation
환생이 아니다
acquaintance
아는 사람
Yes
예
I will send you tasks one after another.
차례대로 작업을 보내드리겠습니다.
Good luck
행운을 빌어요
first gateway
첫 번째 게이트웨이
Make our partners happy
파트너를 행복하게 해주세요
Mission starts
임무 시작
LocationBipyo Bar
위치비표바
Bijou Bar
비쥬 바
You read this and it immediately burns.
당신은 이것을 읽고 즉시 불타 버립니다.
Hello
안녕하세요
how?
어떻게?
Why? I would like to know?
왜? 나는 알고 싶다?
Don't hesitate and speak quickly
머뭇거리지 말고 빨리 말하라
Choose a lucky player in this game who is
이 게임에서 행운의 플레이어를 선택하세요.
What is the mechanism?
메커니즘은 무엇입니까?
My level is higher than yours
내 레벨이 너보다 높아
Why don't you choose me?
왜 나를 선택하지 않습니까?
to yourself
너 자신에게
Is there any misunderstanding?
오해가 있나요?
dad's eldest son
아빠의 큰 아들
Get lost, don't make fun of me
길을 잃으세요. 놀리지 마세요.
Have you tried offline missions?
오프라인 미션을 시도해 보셨나요?
how could I know
내가 어떻게 알아
This version is in the game
이 버전은 게임에 포함되어 있습니다.
The most mysterious existence
가장 신비한 존재
And you
당신은요
From a gamer I know
내가 아는 게이머로부터
The first person to receive an invitation
초대장을 가장 먼저 받은 사람
Anyway, no matter what you play
아무튼 무슨 게임을 하든
will be very exciting
매우 흥미로울 것이다
between us
우리 사이
follow me
나를 따라와
What are we doing?
우리는 무엇을하고 있습니까?
then we
그럼 우리는
in a team
팀에서
While experiencing hardship and sadness together
고난과 슬픔을 함께 겪으면서
Play game together
함께 게임하기
let's retire together
같이 은퇴하자
Am I in your heart?
나는 당신의 마음 속에 있습니까?
Offline tasks
오프라인 작업
I'm not qualified
나는 자격이 없습니다
it's not worth it
그것은 가치가 없어
leave
떠나다
Hey
여기요
You don't have a garden, do you?
당신은 정원이 없군요, 그렇죠?
if i play together
내가 같이 놀면
If you don't take me with you in the future
앞으로는 나를 데리고 가지 않으면
You are suffering huge losses.
당신은 엄청난 손실을 입고 있습니다.
Don't worry
괜찮아요
100,000 bonus
100,000 보너스
You won't miss a penny
한 푼도 놓치지 않을 거예요
and
그리고
what else?
또 뭐야?
I think I have another partner.
다른 파트너가 있는 것 같아요.
men and women?
남자와 여자?
Do you have a photo?
사진이 있나요?
I haven't seen it yet
아직 본 적이 없어요
I'll tell you after seeing the pictures.
사진을 보고 말씀드리겠습니다.
I'll hang up the phone
전화 끊을게요
rainy day sister
비오는 날 언니
I found the source
출처를 찾았어요
soon?
곧?
Only 40 minutes have passed
40분밖에 안 지났는데
So did I pass?
그럼 내가 합격한 걸까?
merchandise
상품
I baked it myself
제가 직접 구웠어요
How do you know I'm hungry?
내가 배고픈 걸 어떻게 알죠?
Very tasty
아주 맛있는
Yes or no?
예 혹은 아니오?
I have something to ask
물어볼 게 있어요
explain
설명하다
according to your opinion
당신의 의견에 따르면
Between my sister-in-law and Director Gao
형수와 가오 감독 사이
we get along very well
우리는 아주 잘 지내요
I can recognize it
나는 그것을 인식할 수 있다
I don't think this is normal
내 생각엔 이게 정상이 아닌 것 같아
Eat snacks and work hard
간식먹고 열심히 일하세요
Stop talking nonsense.
말도 안되는 소리는 그만하세요.
It is understood
이해된다
Dootao memory card
두타오 메모리카드
This is some biological research material.
이것은 생물학적 연구 자료입니다.
No. B13
B13호
B13
B13
as you know
아시다시피
Zhenhai Institute of Biology
진하이 생물학 연구소
B13 project
B13 프로젝트
in special attack game
특수 공격 게임에서
This is a popular item.
인기상품입니다.
A lot of people
많은 사람들
I'm looking for information
정보를 찾고 있어요
information price
정보 가격
Very highly recommended
매우 적극 권장
No
아니요
In this special attack game
이 특수 공격 게임에서는
Is there a black market for information trading?
정보 거래를 위한 암시장이 있습니까?
certainly
틀림없이
This game was originally
이 게임은 원래
This is a virtual world of special forces.
이것은 특수 부대의 가상 세계입니다.
via virtual currency
가상 화폐를 통해
You can trade information within the following ranges
다음 범위 내에서 정보를 거래할 수 있습니다.
Zhenhai Institute of Biology
진하이 생물학 연구소
Founded by Zhenhai Group
진하이그룹(Zhenhai Group) 설립
It is a scientific research organization.
과학연구기관입니다.
Belong to biological group
생물학적 그룹에 속해 있습니다.
It is a national key confidentiality department.
국가 핵심 기밀 유지 부서입니다.
So this professor
그럼 이 교수는
perhaps
아마도
We can hide it in this lab.
이 연구실에서 숨길 수 있습니다.
Contact Biological Research Center today.
지금 생물학 연구 센터에 문의하세요.
Learn about B13
B13에 대해 알아보기
Quickly find the source of leaks
누수 원인을 빠르게 찾아보세요
To avoid causing greater losses
더 큰 손실이 발생하지 않도록
Yes, I will deal with it immediately.
네, 즉시 처리하겠습니다.
Wait a moment
잠깐만요
This investigation must be conducted in secret
이번 조사는 비밀리에 진행돼야 한다
informant
피조사자
Keep it to a minimum
최소한으로 유지하세요
at your home
너의 집에서
Your relatives were also there, right?
네 친척들도 거기 있었지?
Yes, my uncle Huang Jiaming.
네, 황자밍 삼촌이에요.
He is the director of the institute
연구소장입니다
I am the deputy leader of the biology team.
저는 생물학팀의 부팀장입니다.
Do you believe?
당신은 믿나요?
no way
안 돼요
Let’s first understand the situation.
먼저 상황을 파악해보자.
ASAP
최대한 빨리
Yes Yes
예 예
well
잘
OK
좋아요
tie
묶다
Huang Daju
황다주
Anna
안나
Can't you make the name a little more fake?
이름을 좀 더 가짜로 만들 수는 없나요?
This name is a bit cheesy
이 이름은 좀 촌스럽네요
If it's tacky, it's fashionable.
끈적거리면 유행이죠.
Which stage is this?
이것은 어느 단계입니까?
Level 28 old knight
레벨 28 늙은 기사
I'll take you with me
내가 당신을 데리고 갈게요
I am in grade 38 this year
저는 올해 38학년이에요
This sister’s study pressure
이 누나의 공부압박
not enough
부족한
I am also 38 years old.
저도 38세입니다.
You have to call me sister
언니라고 불러야 해
18 I can’t stay anymore
18 더 이상 머물 수 없어요
don't underestimate me
나를 과소평가하지 마세요
after
~ 후에
If you get a bonus of 100,000
보너스 100,000을 받으면
all because of me
다 나 때문이야
Have you tried offline missions before?
이전에 오프라인 미션을 시도해 본 적이 있나요?
No, this is my first time
아니요, 이번이 처음이에요
So why blow it?
그럼 왜 날려?
see this situation
이 상황을 봐
We all play offline
우리 모두 오프라인으로 플레이해요
I flew away before I knew it
나도 모르게 날아가버렸어
Okay everyone
알았어 모두들
Our commendation meeting is
우리 표창회는
will start soon
곧 시작됩니다
Our game is
우리 게임은
male and female partners
남성과 여성의 파트너
The two-person system will be hybrid.
2인 체제는 하이브리드가 될 것이다.
victory is
승리는
You will receive a model of the out-of-print ticket.
절판된 티켓 모델을 받게 됩니다.
The prize is 5,000 yuan.
상금은 5,000위안이다.
Join now
지금 가입하세요
The password prompted by the gateway is
게이트웨이에서 묻는 비밀번호는 다음과 같습니다.
it's in the product
제품에 있어요
So let's get started
그럼 시작해 볼까요
Our cows definitely have B13 in them.
우리 소에는 확실히 B13이 들어있습니다.
This is a key project
핵심 프로젝트입니다
The level of secrecy is very high.
비밀 수준이 매우 높습니다.
this material
이 자료
This is the experiment report
실험보고서입니다
I definitely think someone spilled the beans.
분명 누군가가 콩을 흘린 것 같아요.
Experimental research results
실험적 연구 결과
I'm here?
내가 여기 있어요?
tomorrow
내일
Conduct final sample testing
최종 샘플 테스트 실시
If there is no problem
문제가 없다면
The first stage of the experiment is
실험의 첫 번째 단계는
it's over
끝났어
In the laboratory
실험실에서
Can I check it?
확인할 수 있나요?
if
만약에
people in our lab
우리 연구실 사람들
It was leaked.
유출됐네요.
Safety is most important
안전이 가장 중요합니다
I will be there in person tomorrow
내일 직접 갈게요
I gonna go see
보러 갈게
thank you uncle
고마워요 삼촌
Even the old man didn't come back
그 노인조차 돌아오지 않았다.
When you come back you make me feel so bad
네가 돌아오면 내 기분이 너무 안 좋아져
You should drink with me.
당신은 나와 함께 마셔야합니다.
or tonight
아니면 오늘 밤
I can not sleep
나는 잠을 잘 수가 없어
OK
좋아요
What about the child?
아이는 어떻습니까?
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
It's been a while for me too
나도 오랜만이야
I'm old too
나도 늙었어
I'm addicted to games
나는 게임에 중독됐다.
He is such an old player
그 사람 참 오래된 선수야.
What can you achieve?
당신은 무엇을 달성할 수 있나요?
a good job
좋은 직업
I will do it
내가 할게
Can you do it?
당신은 그것을 할 수 있습니다?
What's your lucky number?
당신의 행운의 숫자는 무엇입니까?
Yes
예
There are 5 red gangs left.
이제 5개의 레드 갱단이 남았습니다.
let's see
보자
Let's see what the first goal looks like.
첫 번째 목표가 어떻게 보이는지 살펴보겠습니다.
Pretty 20
꽤 20
Quite 19 points
꽤 19점
Only 11 points left
이제 11포인트 남았습니다
Hongbang can win
홍방이 이길 수 있어
Why?
왜?
so sad
너무 슬퍼
Now
지금
Nambang players have 40 points left.
남방선수들의 승점은 40점 남았습니다.
let's see
보자
about what?
무엇에 대해?
great
엄청난
This is a 20 point double area.
이것은 20포인트 이중 영역입니다.
from the blue side
파란색 쪽에서
I won
내가이 겄어
great
엄청난
ruler
자
Out-of-print standard model
절판된 표준 모델
There is also 5,000 won in cash.
현금 5,000원도 있어요.
So is that so?
그렇다면 그렇습니까?
It's definitely fashionable.
확실히 유행이네요.
I haven't even started the game yet
아직 게임 시작도 안했는데
It has ended
끝났어
What are you doing?
뭐하세요?
No, look at mine.
아니, 내 것 좀 봐.
Hello
안녕하세요
Please give me an iced Coke.
아이스 콜라 주세요.
Thanks
감사해요
Yes
예
How did you get it?
어떻게 얻었 어?
What should I say?
무슨 말을 해야 할까요?
attraction
끌어 당김
I changed it to 1,000 yuan.
1,000원으로 바꿨어요.
The wealth is staggering.
부는 엄청납니다.
I didn't even get the bonus
보너스도 못받았는데
pick it up first
먼저 집어들어
If you enter 1,000 yuan
1,000원을 입력하면
If I could go on a mission with you
너와 함께 임무를 수행할 수 있다면
If I make friends, I've earned it.
친구를 사귀면 나는 그것을 얻은 것입니다.
friend
친구
once in here
여기에 한 번
any clues
어떤 단서도
if you stab me like this
날 이렇게 찌르면
I think this is the password
이게 비밀번호인 것 같아요
Please save your password
비밀번호를 저장해주세요
Yes?
예?
thermos cup
보온병 컵
sit here
여기 앉으세요
i already told you
내가 이미 말했잖아
this
이것
It can't be an ordinary thermos cup.
평범한 보온병이 아닐 수 없습니다.
on this brush
이 브러시에
what is in here
여기에 뭐가 있지?
you can put anything in it
그 안에는 무엇이든 넣을 수 있어요
Wait for task prompts
작업 프롬프트를 기다립니다
OK
좋아요
Then I'll leave the tools to you first.
그럼 먼저 도구를 맡기겠습니다.
I go first
내가 먼저 가
Why not leave your contact information?
연락처를 남겨주시면 어떨까요?
You can find me in the game
게임에서 나를 찾을 수 있어요
Even outside the game
게임 밖에서도
call
부르다
This is about making friends.
이것은 친구를 사귀는 것에 관한 것입니다.
I'm used to taking my time
나는 시간을 보내는 데 익숙하다
See you tomorrow, friends.
내일 봐요, 친구들.
Boss Huang
황보스
let me ask you
내가 너에게 물어볼께
B13 What is the specific research?
B13 구체적인 연구는 무엇인가요?
this
이것
In the field of biological genes
생물학적 유전자 분야에서는
The research project is
연구 프로젝트는
Targeting OC43 virus
OC43 바이러스 표적으로 삼아
Serum antibodies
혈청항체
Asian genes
아시아 유전자
Lack of antibodies against these viruses
이러한 바이러스에 대한 항체가 부족합니다.
B13 serum antibodies
B13 혈청 항체
If you pass clinical
임상에 합격하면
We will fill this gap generation after generation.
우리는 세대를 거쳐 이 격차를 메울 것입니다.
The result of this study is
이 연구의 결과는
Currently around the world
현재 전 세계적으로
This is the most advanced
이것이 가장 진보된
The most important results of the B13 project are
B13 프로젝트의 가장 중요한 결과는 다음과 같습니다.
I have a serum sample for antibodies.
항체에 대한 혈청 샘플이 있습니다.
I have already informed
이미 알려드렸어요
secret director
비밀 감독
I will cooperate
협력하겠습니다
Serum samples for B13 were
B13에 대한 혈청 샘플은 다음과 같습니다.
There are very limited people you can contact.
연락할 수 있는 사람은 매우 제한되어 있습니다.
almost
거의
Only those who participated in the experiment
실험에 참여한 사람만
Who is eligible to take samples?
샘플을 채취할 자격이 있는 사람은 누구입니까?
with project manager
프로젝트 매니저와 함께
Only some researchers take the lead
일부 연구자만이 주도
The result is out
결과가 나왔습니다
It doesn't matter
그것은 중요하지 않습니다
sample
견본
frozen cosmetics
냉동 화장품
Yes
예